Kevin Sander

IT Administrator/Owner - Kevin Sander Consulting

Kent, WA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Kevin-Sander/f6609fd7a3a68f6d

IT professional with over 15 years of experience in administration, on-site support, escalation support, migration, implementation, engineering, installation, configuration and troubleshooting for various technologies for small to medium business environments and includes proficiency in routing, switching, security, and wireless.

Kevin Sander Consulting IT Administrator/Owner 2014

BossIT IT Administrator /Owner 2009 - 2014

The Pinnacle Group Sr Desktop Administrator/Lead Technician 2002 - 2009

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Administrator/Owner

Kevin Sander Consulting -

2014 to Present

2014

Company Overview - Kevin Sander Consulting worked with multiple companies, such as law offices, Doctor Offices, Golf Courses, Restaurants, and Flooring company's. In January 2014 Kevin Sander Consulting migrated Microsoft SBS 2003 to Microsoft SBS 2011. I was able to migrate Active Directory, Exchange and File Server running Microsoft Server 2003.

Responsibilities handled:

- Responsible for day-to-day maintenance of the IT infrastructure which includes onsite administration and support, scheduled installation, terminal services, configuration and troubleshooting activities within a complex network infrastructure.
- Technical responsibilities included, but not limited to the administration, maintaining, installation, and documentation of any type of activity that is being completed which includes procedures, changes to the network, installs, and troubleshooting for LAN/WAN network infrastructure including network components and VoIP technologies such as: routers, switches, servers and firewalls and various specialized applications including desktop technologies.
- Professional responsibilities include, but are not limited to, management, documentation, change management, following company policies and procedures, and schedule as needed reports to management.
- Core technologies handled includes but not limited to, Cisco ASA 5500 Series, Cisco routers (RV220W, various Cisco Switches, IBM servers, Dell Servers and HP Servers.

IT Administrator/Owner

BossIT -

2009 to 2014

Responsibilities handled:

- IT Contractor responsible for day-to-day administration, maintenance, installing, configuring, implementing and level 2 supporting internal LAN/WAN infrastructure for various companies.
- Technical responsibilities included, but were not limited to, administration, implementation, escalation support, on-site support, installation, configuration, and troubleshooting of various LAN/WAN technologies and peripheral devices.
- Professional responsibilities included interdepartmental communications, all administration activities for users, daily tasks and projects with Network Administrator.
- Specific technical projects and task handled includes but not limited to, administration and management of VPN (Site-to-Site, SSL, Remote, etc), migration of LAN/WAN infrastructure for multiple sites.
- Escalation support activities included 2nd/3rd level support for various LAN/WAN issues for edge routers, VoIP, and customer premise equipment across the U.S to investigate, troubleshoot, reconfigure and resolve to resolve issue in a timely manner and as needed technical support and training of new technical professionals and end-users.

IT Administrator/ Lead Technician

The Pinnicale Group -

2002 to 2009

Company Overview - The Pinnacle Group was a Hardware and Computer support company. We sold hardware to San Luis Obispo County Multiple Departments. We also supported 25 different companies. A Few examples of companies that we supported; City of Pismo Beach, Pismo Beach Police Department, and Pismo Beach Fire Department.

Responsibilities handled:

- I was the lead technician of a team of professionals responsible for the day-to-day administration and maintenance of the IT infrastructure to include onsite administration and support, scheduled installation, configuration and troubleshoot activities for county wide phone support and LAN/WAN infrastructure.
- Technical responsibilities include administration, migration, implementation, configuration, add/move changes, upgrade, and troubleshooting of various mission critical technologies within server, network, and mainframe technologies.
- Technologies handled by the team include but not limited to, installation, connectivity, VPN, user access and/ or permissions to local area network (LAN) technologies, wide area network (WAN) technologies, server and enterprise applications and desktop technologies.
- Professional responsibilities included project coordination, administration, following company policies and procedures, documentation, coordinate level 2/3 meetings, and scheduling as needed reports to management.
- I was the lead technician, I had 5 technician that I managed and scheduled on a day to day basis.

EDUCATION

Certificate in General Education/Computer Science

Mt San Jacinto College